Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/trần-thanh-cao-42a611181 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

java

Spring Boot

Hibernate

Trần Thanh Cao

Technical Lead at VNEXT SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED

Vietnam

Summary

5 years of experience in the software development java
Used fluently SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, Oracle, ProgeSQL
Used OOP and Design Pattern
Experience with framework Spring Boot, Hibernate, Struts2,
Hyperledger Fabric, Angular, React JS
Experience with Block chain
Used SVN and Git

Experience

VNEXT SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS PRIVATE LIMITED

2 years 1 month

Teachnical Lead at Vnext Software Co. November 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month) Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nôi, Vietnam

Technical Lead

November 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nôi, Vietnam

5 years of experience in the software development java

Used fluently SQL Server, MySQL, SQLite, Oracle, ProgeSQL

Used OOP and Design Pattern

Experience with framework Spring Boot, Hibernate, Struts2, Hyperledger

Fabric, Angular, React JS

Experience with Block chain

Used SVN and Git

Technical Lead at Vnext Software Co., LTD November 2019 - November 2019 (1 month)

Hanoi, Thành Phố Hà Nội, Vietnam

CO-WELL Co., LTD

Senior Java Developer

December 2017 - Present (4 years)

Page 1 of 2

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology Good, Electronic and telecommunication · (2010 - 2015)

Activity

11/25/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)